Narrator: 1
Speaker: Holidays together are never a good idea.
Believe me, I know. I’ve been there.
And I have a trail of broken friendships to prove it.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: You’re looking forward to relaxing on the beach with Joanna Trollope’s latest
must-read novel, while their mission is to visit every ancient ruin within a 50-mile radius.
Which is all fine if they don’t mind going it alone,
but when they try to make you feel guilty for lying on your lounger, it’s a different story.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: Now, I’m not really a camping kind of girl,
but since this motorhome was like the Waldorf on wheels,
and North American campsites are known for all their mod cons,
I thought that I’d be pretty safe.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: …a week with someone else’s hyperactive toddler is enough
to turn even the most mild-mannered of us into Supernanny.
And you try packing your own children off to bed at a reasonable hour
when theirs are still bouncing off the ceiling at midnight,
hyped up on fizzy drinks and video games.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: I once spent a week in France,
breastfeeding my newborn daughter in a wardrobe because our child-free friends
hadn’t allowed for the vast amount of baggage a baby comes with
and had allocated us the smallest room.
And they were most put out that we couldn’t drop everything
and hit the town at night, like in the old days.